Preliminary Inventory of the United States Army Air Forces, Air Matériel Command T-2, Air Documents Division Translation Section translations
Hoover Institution Archives
- Box 8
  - Schussler: "Ballistic test and measuring equipment of the Herman Goering Institute of Aeronautical Research,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 8: 4)
  - Schade: "Contribution to numerical tables for air-force calculation of the oscillating air-foil in steady subsonic flow,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 8: 5)
  - Hornberger and Köuig: "Decompression to altitude pressures up to 55800 ft: Effect on humans,", 23 September 1941 (Box-folder 8: 6)
  - Nolte: "Drop forging dies with least machining effort,", 1 July 1943 (Box-folder 8: 7)
  - Quick: "Flight mechanical characterstics of the swept wing at normal speeds,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 8: 8)
  - Folders and labels of missing documents, circa 1945 (Box-folder 8: 9)
  - Freise: "Fundamentals on mechanical methods of scribe-recording measurements,", 1942 (Box-folder 8: 10)
  - Plumeyer: "Investigation of infra-red radiation in aircraft,", 10 June 1946 (Box-folder 8: 11)
  - Brennecke: "Lift increase of swept wings,", 17 July 1943 (Box-folder 8: 12)
  - Kruger: "On a new possibility for maximum lift increase of high speed airfoils,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 8: 13)
  - Plato: "On the stability conditions in curve flight,", 1942 (Box-folder 8: 14)
  - Neuber: "On the stability of longitudinally connected bars,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 8: 15)
  - Hertel: "Production design and manufacturing techniques at Messershmitt,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 8: 16)
  - Heybey: "Review of the Schneller theory of wobbling,", 26 July 1945 (Box-folder 8: 17)
  - Jacobs: "Six component tests conducted on 3 sweep wings,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 8: 18)
  - Regenscheit: "Suction flap wing 43015,", 5 October 1944 (Box-folder 8: 19)
  - Gunter: "Suggestions concerning questions submitted by Mr. L.E. Root about experiences with high speed,", 30 November 1945 (Box-folder 8: 20)
  - Eckert and Weise: "The temperature of uncooled turbine blades in a fast stream of gas,", March 1946 (Box-folder 8: 21)
  - Regenscheit: "Tests on a suction wing NACA 23015 with and without curved nose,", 1 December 1940 (Box-folder 8: 22)
  - Quick: "Tests on airscrews with swept curved blade axes,", January 1946 (Box-folder 8: 23)
  - Michael: "Theoretical and experimental foundations for the testing and development of airplane springing systems,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 8: 24)
  - Kussner: "Theory of the oscillating airfoil of large aspect ratio,", 15 April 1946 (Box-folder 8: 25)
  - Gerecke: "Three-component measurements on a rectangular airfoil profile NACA 23012-64 with fore and back split flaps of different position along the chord,", 1 March 1946 (Box-folder 8: 26)
  - Focke-Wulf Aircraft, Inc: "TL - fighter with He S 011 engine: design and production study,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 8: 27)
  - Koeller: "Torsional stiffness of oblique box spars"; "Proposed stress calculations of an oblique box spar on swept-back wings,", 19 February 1945 (Box-folder 8: 28)
  - Maruhn: Transparencies of graphs, circa 1945 (Box-folder 8: 29)
  - Kusters: "Triple prism recorder (For optical recording of displacement-time diagrams),", March 1946 (Box-folder 8: 30)
- Box 9
  - Wysocki: "3 component tests on aircraft snow-runners,", 15 March 1941 (Box-folder 9: 1)
  - Ritter: "3-component tests on Deuerlilie F-25 in the 2.8 m. dia. high velocity tunnel of the LFA,", 12 January 1944 (Box-folder 9: 2)
  - Helmbold: "A few results of aerodynamic industrial research,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 9: 3)
  - Schiller: "Experimental testing of the law of similarity set up in Report 49/1,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 9: 4)
  - Lindemann: "Flight characteristics and flight performance at high sub-sonic velocities,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 9: 5)
  - Prestele: "Investigation of the flight characterstics of the Me-262 at high speeds on the basis of wind tunnel tests,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 9: 6)
  - Karman: "Investigations on buckling strength,", 1910 (Box-folder 9: 7)
  - Scherer: "Nose intake tests on swept wing,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 9: 8)
  - Solf: "On the dynamic lateral stability of a towed airplane,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 9: 9)
  - Lamla: "On the ray path in Schlieren pictures of simple two dimensional shock waves,", 31 October 1944 (Box-folder 9: 10)
  - Küsner: "Problems of a lifting rotor,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 9: 11)
  - Heinrich: "Report about the works of the Aerodynamical department of the Graf Zeppelin Research Institute,", 26 February 1946 (Box-folder 9: 12)
  - Eichler: "Solution of the integral equation of Possio for the harmonically oscillating airfoil in a compressible medium by reconversion to a linear equation system,", circa 1942 (Box-folder 9: 13)
  - Riegels and Brand: "Stream functions and velocity fields of spatial source-paths and their handy use for the determination of the contour and pressure distribution of rotation-symmetrical bodies, with examples,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 9: 14)
  - Riegels and Brand: (Handwritten draft) "Stream functions and velocity fields of spatial source-paths and their handy use for the determination of the contour and pressure distribution of rotation-symmetrical bodies, with examples,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 9: 15)
  - Luetgebrune: "Supplements to sweep wing tests,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 9: 16)
  - Wegener: "Temporary results on the wind tunnel development of rudders and rudder tabs for the control of the device "Wasserfall",", circa 1945 (Box-folder 9: 17)
  - Nolte: "Weight of cantilever monocoque wings of Dural,", 23 May 1950 (Box-folder 9: 18)
- Box 10
  - Katterbach: "Addendum to the Instationary Wing Theory: Numerical comparison of different approximation theories of the oscillating wing of large aspect ratio,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 10: 1)
  - Mewes: "Aerodynamic data for lateral stability investigations (Advance report),", 1941 (Box-folder 10: 2)
  - Kussner: "Contributions to the instationary airfoil theory" partial translation; "General airfoil theory,", 9 January 1940 (Box-folder 10: 3)
  - Schwarz: "Contributions to the instationary airfoil theory IV,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 10: 4)
  - Schwarz: "Contributions to the instationary airfoil theory VII,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 10: 5)
  - Groth: "Evaluation of density fields around airfoils in wind tunnels by means of optical interference,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 10: 6)
  - Lehmann: "Extensible wing slat" German patent application, 1944 (Box-folder 10: 7)
  - Messerschmitt Co: "Fabricating description of Me 262 (twin turbojet fighter),", circa 1945 (Box-folder 10: 8)
  - Teichmann: "Fundamental considerations for stress analysis in respect to service statistics,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 10: 9)
  - Zobel: "Fundamentally new methods for increasing the performance of high speed aircraft,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 10: 10)
  - Sydow: "Ground pressure tests on skis,", circa 1942 (Box-folder 10: 11)
  - Schiller: "Influence of flat tail fins in the front of the plate subject to airflow on its oscillation behavior,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 10: 12)
  - Ludwieg/Weber: "Influence of the sweeping of controls upon the drag and the pressure point location of a vane-stabilized long projectile in super sonic speeds,", circa 1944 (Box-folder 10: 13)
  - Weissenger: "Lift distribution of sweep wings,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 10: 14)
  - Schlaefke: "On force-deflection diagrams of airplane spring struts. Partial report no. 2: Approximation method for the calculation of force-deflection diagrams with a non-linear spring chart and linear or quadratric damping,", 1944 (Box-folder 10: 15)
  - Doetsch: "On velocities attainable in the next few years,", June 1945 (Box-folder 10: 16)
  - Romberg: "Parachute jump from high altitudes,", 23 June 1941 (Box-folder 10: 17)
  - Göthert: "Pressure distribution and impulse loss diagrams of the airfoil 0 00 18 - 1.1 30 at high subsonic velocities,", 12 September 1941 (Box-folder 10: 18)
  - Jacobs: "Pressure distribution tests on swept wings of constant chord in symmetrical flow,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 10: 19)
  - Küsner: "Problems of a lifting rotor,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 10: 20)
  - Matossi & Passoth: "Pyroelectric investigations,", 10 September 1944 (Box-folder 10: 21)
  - Tietjems: "Relation between the probability of hits and target accuracy between the various types of attacks from airplane to airplane,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 10: 22)
  - Stüper: "Report upon the activity of the Institute for Flight Research,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 10: 23)
  - Schulze: "Second report on the ranges of groud radar equipment against aircraft, flying at high altitudes,", 18 October 1944 (Box-folder 10: 24)
  - Schrode: "Stiffnesses of various tires,", 16 October 1941 (Box-folder 10: 25)
  - Fyertag: "Subsonic and supersonic wind tunnel measurements on the stabilization of the long range rocket Rh Z M 4,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 10: 26)
  - Hawkins: "Vibration engineering activities of Messerschmitt,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 10: 27)
  - Messerschmidt Co.: "Weight analysis of the Me 262 A-1,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 10: 28)
  - Hantsche/Wendt: "Wind tunnel corrections for compressible streams,", 22 August 1940 (Box-folder 10: 29)
  - Feyertag: "Wind tunnel tests on a model of an SE 1000 bomb at subsonic speeds,", 1942 (Box-folder 10: 30)
  - Ludwieg: "Wind tunnel tests on a model of the flak-rocket "Rheintochter" at sub- and supersonic speeds,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 10: 31)
  - Krueger: "Wind tunnel tests on a reworked Mustang profile with nose flap,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 10: 32)
  - Weber: "Wind tunnel tests on Baake-projectiles,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 10: 33)
  - Unidentified papers with pages missing, circa 1945 (Box-folder 10: 34)
- Box 11
  - Weber: "3-component tests on the projectile form R 100 BS in the supersonic wind tunnel,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 11: 1)
  - Puffert/Bolkow: "3-component wind tunnel tests on swept wings and on a swept wing complete model,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 11: 2)
  - Möller: "6-component systematic tests on wing-fuselage combinations with swept wings of constant chord,", 21 August 1943 (Box-folder 11: 3)
  - Scholkemeirer: "6-component tests on three swept wings with and without fuselage,", 20 January 1944 (Box-folder 11: 4)
  - Möller: "6-component tests on wing-fuselage arrangements, Part II: Rectangular wing NACA 23012 with rotation ellipsoid 1:7,", 3 April 1941 (Box-folder 11: 5)
  - Möller: "6-component tests on wing fuselage combination, Part III: Rectangular wing NACA 23012 with rotation ellipsoid 1:7 and triaxial ellipsoid; trapezoidal wing NACA 23012 with rotation ellipsoid 1:7,", 6 January 1942 (Box-folder 11: 6)
  - Möller: "6-component tests on wing-fuselage combinations with a swept trapezoidal wing,", 12 July 1944 (Box-folder 11: 7)
  - "Air documents division document process sheet,", 1 October 1946 (Box-folder 11: 8)
  - Preussler: "The calibration of cold-drawn sections,", 10 November 1949 (Box-folder 11: 9)
  - Kraus: "Discussion on vertical and slant shots of the A-4B rocket, its gliding path, boundary layer temperature and skin temperature,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 11: 10)
  - Kress: "Economical manufacturing accuracies,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 11: 11)
  - Walchner & Roth: "The effect of fuselage and engine nacelles on the characterstics of a swept back wing at high speeds,", July 1940 (Box-folder 11: 12)
  - Coremann: "Equipment used to determine the effect of sound and oscillations on the human body,", 10 November 1937 (Box-folder 11: 13)
  - Transparencies for Mülemann: "Experimental investigation on an axial blower stage" dissertation, 1946 (Box-folder 11: 14)
  - Plock & Eberspaecher: "Experimental welds for steel spars of the Fw-191 bomber, and strength properties of cold-worked flange angles,", December 1941 (Box-folder 11: 15)
  - Rott: "The field of a fast moving sound source,", 15 January 1945 (Box-folder 11: 16)
  - Schlippe & Dietrich: "Flutter of a wheel with pneumatic tire,", 1943 (Box-folder 11: 17)
  - Teichmann: "Grundsätzliche Betrachtungen über Festigkeitsversuche im Sinne der Betriebsstatistik,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 11: 18)
  - "Inspection & installation instructions for the ejection canopy FW 190,", October 1944 (Box-folder 11: 19)
  - DVL: "Miscellaneous wind tunnel data on laminar flow,", 15 May 1941 (Box-folder 11: 20)
  - Bilharz: "On single-dimensional free oscillations at non-linear restoring force,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 11: 21)
  - Report missing title page and introduction, circa 1945 (Box-folder 11: 22)
- Box 12
  - Ruff: "Attempts at rescue from high altitudes,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 12: 1)
  - Schlinger: "Bismuth sulfide thermo-elements,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 12: 2)
  - Gothert/Kawalki: "Compressible flow about various flap profiles near sonic velocity,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 12: 3)
  - Arado & Kopperschmidt Companies: "Conception of invention disclosure: "Stress-absorbing connection",", circa 1945 (Box-folder 12: 4)
  - Eichler: "Construction of kernels for the solution of singular integral equations of the first kind, especially with differential kernels,", 1942 (Box-folder 12: 5)
  - Huber: "Development and research on impulse-type heater for the moving of gases,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 12: 6)
  - Hornung: "Efficiency comparison of TL-drive pursuit planes,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 12: 7)
  - Lehmann: "Extensible wing slat,", 1944 (Box-folder 12: 8)
  - "High-speed, wind-tunnel tests on NACA airfoil 0015-64,", February 1940 (Box-folder 12: 9)
  - Lamla: "The influence of the jet boundary in high velocity wind tunnels,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 12: 10)
  - Göthert/Richter: "Measurements on the NACA 0015-64 airfoil with various chords in the high-speed wind tunnel,", 28 November 1940 (Box-folder 12: 11)
  - Leiss: "On gust-excited tail oscillations,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 12: 12)
  - Lechewski & Lockmann: "On the chemical de-icing of airplane skis,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 12: 13)
  - Maruhn: "Pressure distribution on a tri-axial ellipsoid body uniformly moved in a straight line,", 2 February 1940 (Box-folder 12: 14)
  - I. G. Farbenindustrie: "Process for producing easily soluble polyamides,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 12: 15)
  - Research Information Service: "Process for producing transparent condensates or polymers from linear bifunctional compounds,", 1949 (Box-folder 12: 16)
  - Merbt: "The rotational sound of airscrews,", 31 October 1944 (Box-folder 12: 17)
  - Kramer: "Skid-landings with 50 kg/m2 wing load,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 12: 18)
  - Busemann: "Sweptback wings at high speeds,", April 1943 (Box-folder 12: 19)
  - Mester: "Temperature measurements on shell structures,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 12: 20)
  - Koeller: "Temporary report on the torsional stiffness of oblique box spars,", 19 February 1945 (Box-folder 12: 21)
  - Brödel: "Theory of two-dimensional symmetrical catch-diffusors,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 12: 22)
  - Liess/Weber: "Three component test on a vane-stabilized long missile in the super sonic wind tunnel,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 12: 23)
  - Küch: "Transparent synthetic materials for the glazing of aircraft,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 12: 24)
  - Nolte: "Weight of cantilever monocoque wings of Dural,", 23 May 1950 (Box-folder 12: 25)
  - Stensel: "Wings of plywood lath grid sandwich construction,", 12 September 1944 (Box-folder 12: 26)
  - Stray page of a report, circa 1945 (Box-folder 12: 27)
- Box 13
  - Multhopp: "Aerodynamic principles of the Lorin-Jet unit,", June 1945 (Box-folder 13: 1)
  - "The automatic air-plot chart,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 13: 2)
  - Moeller: "Development of wave absorbing layers,", November 1943 (Box-folder 13: 3)
  - Naumann: "Efficiencies of diffusers at high subsonic velocities,", December 1942 (Box-folder 13: 4)
  - Lindemann: "High speed measurements on the Me 262 airplanes,", September 1942 (Box-folder 13: 5)
  - Mayer: "Load-distribution variation of an airplane during landing-flap deflection,", August 1946 (Box-folder 13: 6)
  - Curtiss-Wright Engineering department: "Pressure distribution measurements on two arrow wings of constant chord (sweepback angle - 30 degrees and 45 degrees for asymmetrical airflow,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 13: 7)
  - Handel: "Radar anti-jamming measures,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 13: 8)
  - "Radio direction finder,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 13: 9)
  - Novotny: "Wind tunnel measurements on an Me-163B sweptback-wing rocket interceptor - Vol I and II,", February 1943 (Box-folder 13: 10)
- Box 14
  - Greil: "Basic data for the calculation of heat transfer in combustion chambers,", April 1942 (Box-folder 14: 1)
  - Kappus: "Bombardment of fixed targets with large area, from great distance, by gliding bombs,", 13 April 1943 (Box-folder 14: 2)
  - Schlichting: "Boundary layer theory,", 1 December 1941 (Box-folder 14: 3)
  - Schrode: "Construction and load capacity of airplane tires,", April 1940 (Box-folder 14: 4)
  - Zehlendorf: "Decimeter communication equipment,", 4 May 1942 (Box-folder 14: 5)
  - Luckert: "Lift distribution according to Weissinger,", March 1944 (Box-folder 14: 6)
  - Mallach & Zinke: "Radiation and matching of hollow conductors and horn attennas with dielectric end plates,", 25 February 1948 (Box-folder 14: 7)
  - Herold: "Radio-guided and target-seeking control mechanisms,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 14: 8)
  - Peppinger: "Remote indicator with large torque,", 17 August 1941 (Box-folder 14: 9)
  - Aschenbrenner: "Some new applications of frequency modulation,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 14: 10)
  - Meyer: "The two dimensional phenomena of motion in a gas flowing at supersonic velocity,", August 1945 (Box-folder 14: 11)
- Box 15
  - Wagner: "Boundary layer effects on AF 252 transport,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 15: 1)
  - Jacobs: "Calculation of the down-wash coefficient for various wing forms,", 11 November 1943 (Box-folder 15: 2)
  - Kraft: "Diffraction of electric waves on sea waves,", 20 December 1944 (Box-folder 15: 3)
  - Hempel: "Drag of jet engine nacelles at high Mach number, effect of shape and Reynold's Number,", 22 December 1943 (Box-folder 15: 4)
  - Meyer-Rässler: "Formfüllungsvermögen von Druckgusslegierungen,", 23 August 1946 (Box-folder 15: 5)
  - Scharn: "Numerical solution of algebraic equations of higher degree, having only complex roots, by means of the elemination method,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 15: 6)
  - Menzen & Patterson: "On magnesium ingot casting,", October 1943 (Box-folder 15: 7)
  - Sauer: "Report on pressure distribution on body of revolution WK 581E at 0 degree angle of attack,", May 1942 (Box-folder 15: 8)
  - Busemann: "The separation of boundary layer near the speed of sound,", June 1939 (Box-folder 15: 9)
  - Mayer & Bender: "Test data on Frits I air-to-surface guided missile,", 22 April 1942 (Box-folder 15: 10)
  - Hülster: "The triode at shortest waves,", November 1944 (Box-folder 15: 11)
  - Riegels: "Ungleichförmigkeiten der strömung und ihr Eínfluss auf einen Flügel,", August 1946 (Box-folder 15: 12)
- Box 16
  - Gottingen: "Aerodynamic design problems of Gottinger suction aircraft,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 16: 1)
  - Runkel: "Aerodynamic measurements on the experimental and testing aircraft DFS 332,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 16: 2)
  - U.S. Naval Technical Mission in Europe: "Air craft engines - additional and temporary supercharge by the use of nitrous oxide N20 in the air,", July 1945 (Box-folder 16: 3)
  - Kane: "Bids on wing spars,", February 1941 (Box-folder 16: 4)
  - Cassens: "Code symbols for loading,", circa 1943 (Box-folder 16: 5)
  - Heinkel: "Construction directives: Riveting, general,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 16: 6)
  - Neubauer, Schaeffer, Viehmann: "Coupling of airplane antennas with the aircraft wiring system and effect of various shieldings,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 16: 7)
  - Walter & Heger: "Experimental and theoretical investigations on the flutter behavior of the arrow wing,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 16: 8)
  - "Friction drag reduction by a prolongation of laminar boundary layer flow, especially by means of boundary layer suction bleeding,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 16: 9)
  - Hoerner: "Influence of compressibility on drag,", 1 January 1944 (Box-folder 16: 10)
  - Hertl: "Method of purifying metal melts,", circa 1944 (Box-folder 16: 11)
  - Willms & Ernsthauson: "New investigations on airplane noises,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 16: 12)
  - Schardin & Schultze: "Nouvelle méthode pour la radiogeniométrie en ondes courtes et ultra-courtes,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 16: 13)
  - Gassner: "On previous results of stress analysis in view of service statistics,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 16: 14)
  - Wegener: "On the "S-trend" of controllability curves on the device "Wasserfall",", 3 March 1945 (Box-folder 16: 15)
  - Noeggerath: "Report on code names for rocket fuels,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 16: 16)
  - Hullman: "Report on the status of knowledge on the construction of fuel-tight wings as of May 1944," (Box-folder 16: 17)
  - Focke-Wulf: "Safe shear flow for skin and spar web of F-W wing,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 16: 18)
  - Hobusch: "Spotwelded steel spars,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 16: 19)
  - Froehlich: "Steel vs Duraluminum in wing construction,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 16: 20)
  - Krüger: "Wind tunnel tests on a 4-engine complete model with - and without boundary layer control,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 16: 21)
  - Hansen: "Wings of constant chord with sweep and twist in yawing,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 16: 22)
  - Hilscher: "The wobble-error in a gyro compass,", 1943 (Box-folder 16: 23)
- Box 17
  - Lehnert: "The aerodynamic development of the long distance rocket A-9 (A-4b),", circa 1945 (Box-folder 17: 1)
  - Osken: "Annular ring horn radiator for the reduction of reverse radiation,", October 1944 (Box-folder 17: 2)
  - Rave: "Anti-icing paste for aircraft,", December 1942 (Box-folder 17: 3)
  - Messerschmidt Co.: "Bibliography on spin,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 17: 4)
  - "Circuit diagrams of the Me-262 electrical systems,", 22 July 1949 (Box-folder 17: 5)
  - Kosel: "Committee meeting on production of steel spars,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 17: 6)
  - Richter: "Comparison of approximation methods for calculating the pressure distribution on profiles at subcritical mach numbers with measurements,", October 1942 (Box-folder 17: 7)
  - Schlaefke: "Comparison of "buffered and unbuffered" spring shocks on landing gear,", 1943 (Box-folder 17: 8)
  - Swiss Aerotechnical Society: "Comparison of to-day's long range transport airplanes with the new English turbo drive types,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 17: 9)
  - Schade: "Contribution to numerical tables for air-force calculation of the oscillating air-foil in steady subsonic flow,", December 1944 (Box-folder 17: 10)
  - Tollmien: "Equations for adiabatic but rotational steady gas flows without friction,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 17: 11)
  - Ritz: "Exhaust gas-air mixture for anti-icing,", September 1943 (Box-folder 17: 12)
  - Weissinger: "Forces and moments of a wing in yaw,", 8 February 1946 (Box-folder 17: 13)
  - Schiller: "Generalization of the similarity law of "252",", circa 1945 (Box-folder 17: 14)
  - Rotta: "Graph showing relations between fuel capacity, range, speed, thrust and altitude for twin-engine jet bomber,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 17: 15)
  - Sydow: "Ground pressure tests on skis,", circa 1942 (Box-folder 17: 16)
  - Strassl: "Investigation on a twisted swept wing with various fuselage arrangements at high velocities,", 3 October 1940 (Box-folder 17: 17)
  - Ludwig & Geissler: "Longitudinal guidance of winged missiles,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 17: 18)
  - Heintzelmann: "Main spar flange of the Fw300A with 1620 steel treated to 120 kg/mm2,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 17: 19)
  - Winkler: "A mechanical evaluation method for interferometer photographs,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 17: 20)